{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of Star Wars: The Force Awakens.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is the stormtrooper defector?",
      "answers": ["Finn", "Rey", "Poe"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the scavenger on Jakku?",
      "answers": ["Rey", "Finn", "Han"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Kylo Ren's weapon?",
      "answers": ["Saber", "Blaster", "Bow"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Han's co-pilot?",
      "answers": ["Chewie", "Leia", "Rey"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the First Order's base?",
      "answers": ["Stark", "Death", "Hoth"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the Resistance pilot?",
      "answers": ["Poe", "Finn", "Han"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Rey's mentor?",
      "answers": ["Han", "Luke", "Leia"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who wields a blue lightsaber?",
      "answers": ["Rey", "Finn", "Poe"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What droid has the map?",
      "answers": ["BB-8", "R2", "C-3PO"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader of the First Order?",
      "answers": ["Snoke", "Kylo", "Hux"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who fights Kylo Ren in the forest?",
      "answers": ["Rey", "Finn", "Han"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Millennium Falcon?",
      "answers": ["Ship", "Star", "Base"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the former stormtrooper?",
      "answers": ["Finn", "Rey", "Poe"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the General of the Resistance?",
      "answers": ["Leia", "Han", "Poe"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What planet is Rey from?",
      "answers": ["Jakku", "Hoth", "Endor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Kylo Ren's father?",
      "answers": ["Han", "Luke", "Snoke"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Kylo Ren's real name?",
      "answers": ["Ben", "Anakin", "Luke"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the Supreme Leader?",
      "answers": ["Snoke", "Kylo", "Hux"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What color is Rey's lightsaber?",
      "answers": ["Blue", "Red", "Green"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the pilot's droid?",
      "answers": ["BB-8", "R2", "C-3PO"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
